[
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "category": "Web Development: JavaScript",
    "question": "What keyword is used to declare a variable that can't be reassigned?",
    "correct_answer": "const",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "var",
      "let",
      "fixed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "category": "Web Development: JavaScript",
    "question": "In JavaScript, == and === operators are identical.",
    "correct_answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Web Development: JavaScript",
    "question": "Which method is used to add an element to the end of an array?",
    "correct_answer": "push()",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "append()",
      "add()",
      "insert()"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "category": "Web Development: JavaScript",
    "question": "JavaScript is a statically typed language.",
    "correct_answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "category": "Web Development: JavaScript",
    "question": "What will be the output of console.log(typeof [])?",
    "correct_answer": "object",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "array",
      "list",
      "undefined"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "category": "Web Development: JavaScript",
    "question": "The let keyword declares a block-scoped variable.",
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "category": "Web Development: JavaScript",
    "question": "Which method is used to remove the last element from an array?",
    "correct_answer": "pop()",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "remove()",
      "delete()",
      "slice()"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "category": "Web Development: JavaScript",
    "question": "Arrow functions in JavaScript always need curly braces {}.",
    "correct_answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "type": "text",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "category": "Web Development: JavaScript",
    "question": "Complete the code to create a function:\n_______ greet(name) {\n  return `Hello, ${name\n      }!`;\n    }",
    "correct_answers": ["function"]
  },
  {
    "type": "text",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "category": "Web Development: JavaScript",
    "question": "Complete the code to create a Promise object:\nconst myPromise = new ________;",
    "correct_answers": ["Promise()"]
  }
]